Finding Aid for the Music Center records LSC.3261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 11: Music Center Reference Library, 1872-2018
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,088, Folder 1-7)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,089, Folder 1-9)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,090, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,091, Folder 1-7)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,092, Folder 1-7)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,093, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,094, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,095, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,096, Folder 1-8)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,097, Folder 1-15)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,098, Folder 1-13)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,099, Folder 1-10)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,100, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,101, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,102, Folder 1-8)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,103, Folder 1-5)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,104, Folder 1-8)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,105, Folder 1-5)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,106, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,107, Folder 1-9)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,108, Folder 1-8)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,109, Folder 1-17)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,110, Folder 1-8)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,111, Folder 1-10)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,112, Folder 1-5)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,113, Folder 1-6)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,114, Folder 1-9)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,115, Folder 1-7)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,116, Folder 1-3)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,117, Folder 1-3)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,118, Folder 1-7)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,119, Folder 1-5)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,120, Folder 1-4)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,121, Folder 1-5)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,122, Folder 1-3)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,123, Folder 1-3)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,124, Folder 1-4)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,125, Folder 1-4)
  - Monographs, undated (Box 2,126, Folder 1-2)
  - Notes: The Quarterly Journal of the Music Library Association, v. 36, no. 1 - v. 40, no. 1. New York., 1979 September-1983 September (Box 2,127, Folder 1-16)
  - Notes: The Quarterly Journal of the Music Library Association, v. 40, no. 2 - v. 41, no. 2. New York., 1983 December-1984 December (Box 2,128, Folder 1-8)
    This box also contains an issue of Forbes dated 2001 December 24 and 2 issues of Fortune dated 2002 January 7 and 21.
  - Theatre Arts Monthly, v. 20, no. 1 - v. 21, no. 3. New York., 1936 January - 1937 March (Box 2,129, Folder 1-15)
  - Theatre Arts Monthly, v. 21, no. 5 - v. 23, no. 6. New York., 1937 May-1939 June (Box 2,130, Folder 1-13)
  - New York Theatre Critics' Reviews, v. 33, no. 1 - v. 35, no. 25. New York., 1972 January-1974 December (Box 2131, Folder 1-3)
  - New York Theatre Critics' Reviews, v. 36, no. 1 - v. 38, no. 24. New York., 1975 January-1977 December (Box 2,132, Folder 1-3)
  - New York Theatre Critics' Reviews, v. 39, no. 1 - v. 41, no. 21. New York., 1978 January-1980 December (Box 2,133, Folder 1-3)
  - New York Theatre Critics' Reviews, v. 42, no. 1 - v. 44, no. 19. New York., 1981 January-1983 December (Box 2,134, Folder 1-3)
  - New York Theatre Critics' Reviews, v. 45, no. 1 - v. 45, no. 18. New York., 1984 January- 1984 December (Box 2,135, Folder 1-3)
    This box also contains George C. D. Odell's 1927 Annals of the New York Stage, v. 1 and v. 2. New York.
  - Annals of the New York Stage, v. 3 - v. 4. New York., 1928 (Box 2,136, Folder 1-2)
  - Annals of the New York Stage, v. 5 - v. 6. New York., 1931 (Box 2,137, Folder 1-2)
  - Annals of the New York Stage, v. 7 - v. 8. New York., 1931, 1936 (Box 2,138, Folder 1-2)
  - Annals of the New York Stage, v. 9 - v. 10. New York., 1937-1938 (Box 2,139, Folder 1-2)
  - Annals of the New York Stage, v. 11 - v. 12. New York., 1939-1940 (Box 2,140, Folder 1-2)
  - Annals of the New York Stage, v. 13 - v. 14. New York., 1942, 1945 (Box 2,141, Folder 1-2)
  - Annals of the New York Stage, v. 15. New York., 1949 (Box 2,142, Folder 1)
  - High Performance, v. 9, no. 1 - v. 16, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1986-1993 (Box 2143, Folder 1-21)
  - High Performance, v. 16, no. 2 - v. 20, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1993-1997 (Box 2,144, Folder 1-14)
  - Musical America, v. 61, no. 3. New York., 1941, 1977-1978 (Box 2,145, Folder 1-3)
    This box also contains two Musical America International Directories of the Performing Arts.
  - The Stage. New York., 1934 July-1935 December (Box 2,146, Folder 1-20)
    This box also contains Pictorial California and the Pacific, v. 42, no. 3 and v. 42, no. 6. These issues are dated Holiday 1967 and Summer 1967 and were published in Los Angeles.
  - Stage. New York., 1936 August-1937 May (Box 2,147, Folder 1-10)
- Series 12: Music Center memorabilia and ephemera, 1919-2018
  The Music Center memorabilia and ephemera ranges in date from 1919-2018 and contains window card inventories; LAPO, Lease events, Mark Taper Forum, Ahmanson Theatre, and Music Center Opera Association New York City Opera window cards; oversize posters; Music Center, Center Theatre Group, Glorya Kaufman Presents Dance at the Music Center, Hollywood Bowl, Spotlight Awards ephemera; WDCH, and LA Opera ephemera; oversize Otto Rothschild photographs; Black Business Dance at the Music Center resolutions; Dorothy Chandler diploma and awards; Charles A. Buffum portrait; Buff Chandler portrait by Henry Koerner; and a Dorothy Chandler arts and education bell.
  - Window card inventories, 1968-2000 (Box 2,148, Folder 1-10)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra window cards, 1965-1984 (Box 2,149, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra window cards, 1984-1994 (Box 2,150, Folder 1)
  - Lease events window cards, A, undated (Box 2,151, Folder 1)
  - Lease events window cards, B-F, undated (Box 2,152, Folder 1)
  - Lease events window cards, G-K, undated (Box 2,153, Folder 1)
  - Lease events window cards, L-M, undated (Box 2,154, Folder 1)
  - Lease events window cards, R-T, undated (Box 2,155, Folder 1)
  - Lease events window cards, V-Y, undated (Box 2,156, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum season window cards, 1969-1989 (Box 2,157, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, A-C, undated (Box 2,158, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, D-F, undated (Box 2,159, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, G-H, undated (Box 2,160, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, I-L, undated (Box 2,161, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, M, undated (Box 2,162, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, N-R, undated (Box 2,163, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, S, undated (Box 2,164, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, T, undated (Box 2,165, Folder 1)
  - Mark Taper Forum window cards, U-Z, undated (Box 2,166, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre season window cards and A-B, undated (Box 2,167, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, C, undated (Box 2,168, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, D-E, undated (Box 2,169, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, F, undated (Box 2,170, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, G-H, undated (Box 2,171, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, I-L, undated (Box 2,172, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, M, undated (Box 2,173, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window, M and P, undated (Box 2,174, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, R-S, undated (Box 2,175, Folder 1)
  - Ahmanson Theatre window cards, T-W, undated (Box 2,176, Folder 1)
  - Music Center Opera Association New York City Opera window cards, 1968-1974 (Box 2,177, Folder 1)
  - Music Center Opera Association New York City Opera window cards, 1974-1982 (Box 2,178, Folder 1)
  - Oversize posters, undated (Box 2,179, Folder 1)
  - Oversize posters, undated (Box 2,180, Folder 1)
  - Ephemera binder, 1986-1995 (Box 2,181, Folder 1-23)
  - Music Center ephemera, 2005-2007 (Box 2,182, Folder 1-11)
  - Center Theatre Group and Glorya Kaufman Presents Dance at the Music Center ephemera, 2005-2018 (Box 2,183, Folder 1-6)
    Folder 5 contains two The Light in the Piazza CDs.
  - Hollywood Bowl and Spotlight Awards ephemera, 2006-2014 (Box 2,184, Folder 1-7)
  - Center Theatre Group ephemera, 2006-2018 (Box 2,185, Folder 1-7)
  - Walt Disney Concert Hall ephemera, 2006-2017 (Box 2,186, Folder 1-5)
  - LA Opera ephemera, 2008-2017 (Box 2,187, Folder 1-5)
  - Oversize Otto Rothschild photographs, undated (Box 2,188, Folder 1)
  - Black Business Dance at the Music Center resolutions, 2003 (Box 2,189, Folder 1-3)
  - Awards and ephemera, 1964-2008 (Box 2,190, Folder 1-5)
  - Dorothy Chandler diploma and awards, 1919-1964 (Box 2,191, Folder 1-4)
  - Dorothy Chandler awards, 1962, 1980 (Box 2,192, Folder 1-3)
  - Dorothy Chandler awards and Center Theatre Group ephemera, circa 1960s-1990s (Box 2,193, Folder 1-10)
  - Charles A. Buffum portrait, undated (Box 2,194, Folder 1)
  - Buff Chandler portrait by Henry Koerner, 1964 December 18 (Box 2,195, Folder 1)
  - Dorothy Chandler arts and education bell, 1979 May (Box 2,196, Folder 1)